{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_7_A4CKJZ",
                "player_15_A4CKJZ",
                "player_5_A4CKJZ",
                "player_10_A4CKJZ",
                "player_12_A4CKJZ",
                "player_3_A4CKJZ"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                7,
                15,
                5,
                10,
                12,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "liedown",
                "stand",
                "liedown",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    9834.446,
                    24384.727,
                    1321.666,
                    0,
                    -123.12580851865005,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    10027.22,
                    24536.814,
                    1321.588,
                    0,
                    126.97727590192306,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9591.987,
                    24763.831,
                    1325.207,
                    0,
                    -13.059170576222044,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9745.952,
                    24761.093,
                    1321.826,
                    0,
                    72.50765707259416,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9762.171,
                    24900.793,
                    1322.242,
                    0,
                    -34.163364690693925,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9496.413,
                    24751.936,
                    1327.559,
                    0.0,
                    -0.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_A4CKJZ"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    9863.41,
                    24820.506,
                    1521.711,
                    0,
                    49.88648850916283,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            9473.656,
            24221.717,
            1321.588
        ],
        "sample_radius": 937.8248753715212
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            10263.602,
            24422.507,
            1331.341,
            0,
            150.88853287598195,
            0
        ],
        [
            9437.052,
            24054.194,
            1321.587,
            0,
            63.51548074403993,
            0
        ],
        [
            9230.097,
            25052.084,
            1343.583,
            0,
            -33.378456624671806,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a state of lying down in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many people are in a crouched position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are both male and bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people are wearing glasses in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Excluding those who are bald, how many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene have a medium skin tone?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many drones are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many women in the scene are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. hold something",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in a brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. hold something",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. hold something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. hold something",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. hold something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. hold something",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "A. hold something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Slightly below and to the left of",
                    "B. Slightly above and to the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Slightly above and to the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}